Engineering and Applied Sciences, College of; Records ua670
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Administrative Records, 2000-2015; 2; 15 cubic ft.
  - Academic Advisory Committee, 2007 (Box 15 (2-Administrative Records), Item 4)
  - Interdisciplinary Ph.D. Program in Information Science, 2009 (Box 15 (2-Administrative Records), Item 5)
  - Interdisciplinary Ph.D. Program in Information Science, 2009 (Box 15 (2-Administrative Records), Item 6)
  - Interdisciplinary Ph.D. Program in Information Science, 2009 (Box 15 (2-Administrative Records), Item 7)
  - Background Materials: NYS Office of Cyber Security and Infrastructure, 2007 (Box 15 (2-Administrative Records), Item 8)
  - Background Materials: NYS Office of Cyber Security and Infrastructure, 2007 (Box 15 (2-Administrative Records), Item 9)
  - Dean's Office: College of Computing And Information, 2012 (Box 15 (2-Administrative Records), Item 10)
  - The Institute for Fianancial Market Regulations, Undated (Box 15 (2-Administrative Records), Item 11)
  - Watervliet Innovation Center, Undated (Box 15 (2-Administrative Records), Item 12)
  - Homeland Solutions: Training Development-Procurment, Undated (Box 15 (2-Administrative Records), Item 13)